[{"answer": "Good evening, folks.  Welcome to Southern Caf.  How are you this evening", "docId": "11-09", "aSentId": 11, "question": "", "qSentId": 10},{"answer": " Were fine, thanks", "docId": "11-09", "aSentId": 12, "question": "Good evening, folks.  Welcome to Southern Caf.  How are you this evening", "qSentId": 11},{"answer": " Great.  Im Andy and Im going to be your waiter tonight", "docId": "11-09", "aSentId": 13, "question": " Were fine, thanks", "qSentId": 12},{"answer": " Hi, Andy", "docId": "11-09", "aSentId": 14, "question": " Great.  Im Andy and Im going to be your waiter tonight", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": " Can I start you off with anything to drink", "docId": "11-09", "aSentId": 15, "question": " Hi, Andy", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " What beers do you have", "docId": "11-09", "aSentId": 16, "question": " Can I start you off with anything to drink", "qSentId": 15},{"answer": " On tap we have Heineken, Miller, St. Paulys Girl, Guinness, and Sam Adams", "docId": "11-09", "aSentId": 17, "question": " What beers do you have", "qSentId": 16},{"answer": " Hmmm.  Id like to try something light and refreshing.  Can you recommen", "docId": "11-09", "aSentId": 21, "question": " On tap we have Heineken, Miller, St. Paulys Girl, Guinness, and Sam Adams", "qSentId": 20},{"answer": " Actually, right now we have a Rogue pale ale in the bottle.  Its very light an", "docId": "11-09", "aSentId": 23, "question": " Hmmm.  Id like to try something light and refreshing.  Can you recommen", "qSentId": 22},{"answer": " OK.  Ill try that one", "docId": "11-09", "aSentId": 32, "question": " Actually, right now we have a Rogue pale ale in the bottle.  Its very light an", "qSentId": 31},{"answer": " And for you, mam", "docId": "11-09", "aSentId": 33, "question": " OK.  Ill try that one", "qSentId": 32},{"answer": "Do you have a wine list", "docId": "11-09", "aSentId": 34, "question": " And for you, mam", "qSentId": 33},{"answer": " Yes, its right here", "docId": "11-09", "aSentId": 35, "question": "Do you have a wine list", "qSentId": 34},{"answer": " Ummm.  I think Ill have a glass of the house Chardonnay", "docId": "11-09", "aSentId": 36, "question": " Yes, its right here", "qSentId": 35},{"answer": " Very good", "docId": "11-09", "aSentId": 37, "question": " Ummm.  I think Ill have a glass of the house Chardonnay", "qSentId": 36},{"answer": " Thank you", "docId": "11-09", "aSentId": 37, "question": " Very good", "qSentId": 36},{"answer": " Let me tell you about our specials this evening too.  We have a three-chees", "docId": "11-09", "aSentId": 38, "question": " Thank you", "qSentId": 37},{"answer": "Does the lasagna have meat in it", "docId": "11-09", "aSentId": 43, "question": " Let me tell you about our specials this evening too.  We have a three-chees", "qSentId": 42},{"answer": " No.  Its just cheese and tomatoes", "docId": "11-09", "aSentId": 44, "question": "Does the lasagna have meat in it", "qSentId": 43},{"answer": " OK.  Thank you", "docId": "11-09", "aSentId": 45, "question": " No.  Its just cheese and tomatoes", "qSentId": 44},{"answer": " Ill give you a few minutes to look over the menu while I get your drinks", "docId": "11-09", "aSentId": 46, "question": " OK.  Thank you", "qSentId": 45},{"answer": "What are you going to have, Frank", "docId": "11-09", "aSentId": 47, "question": " Ill give you a few minutes to look over the menu while I get your drinks", "qSentId": 46},{"answer": " I dont know.  I cant decide between the chicken pasta on the menu and tha", "docId": "11-09", "aSentId": 48, "question": "What are you going to have, Frank", "qSentId": 47},{"answer": "Fries", "docId": "11-09", "aSentId": 52, "question": " I dont know.  I cant decide between the chicken pasta on the menu and tha", "qSentId": 51},{"answer": " Yeah, I think Im going to have that.  What about you", "docId": "11-09", "aSentId": 53, "question": "Fries", "qSentId": 52},{"answer": " I think Ill have the fish and chips.  That sounds good, doesnt it", "docId": "11-09", "aSentId": 54, "question": " Yeah, I think Im going to have that.  What about you", "qSentId": 53},{"answer": " Ive had that before.  It is good", "docId": "11-09", "aSentId": 55, "question": " I think Ill have the fish and chips.  That sounds good, doesnt it", "qSentId": 54},{"answer": " OK.  Ill try that then", "docId": "11-09", "aSentId": 56, "question": " Ive had that before.  It is good", "qSentId": 55},{"answer": " OK.  Here are your drinks.  Have you folks decided", "docId": "11-09", "aSentId": 57, "question": " OK.  Ill try that then", "qSentId": 56},{"answer": " Yes.  Id like the fish and chips, please", "docId": "11-09", "aSentId": 58, "question": " OK.  Here are your drinks.  Have you folks decided", "qSentId": 57},{"answer": " OK.  Would you like to add a salad or soup to that", "docId": "11-09", "aSentId": 59, "question": " Yes.  Id like the fish and chips, please", "qSentId": 58},{"answer": " Sure.  A salad, please", "docId": "11-09", "aSentId": 63, "question": " OK.  Would you like to add a salad or soup to that", "qSentId": 62},{"answer": " What kind of dressing would you like?  We have Caesar, Thousand Island", "docId": "11-09", "aSentId": 64, "question": " Sure.  A salad, please", "qSentId": 63},{"answer": "Ranch on the side, please", "docId": "11-09", "aSentId": 68, "question": " What kind of dressing would you like?  We have Caesar, Thousand Island", "qSentId": 67},{"answer": " OK.  And you, sir", "docId": "11-09", "aSentId": 69, "question": "Ranch on the side, please", "qSentId": 68},{"answer": "Ill have that double-decker burger, please", "docId": "11-09", "aSentId": 70, "question": " OK.  And you, sir", "qSentId": 69},{"answer": " All right.  Would you like to add a salad or soup to that", "docId": "11-09", "aSentId": 71, "question": "Ill have that double-decker burger, please", "qSentId": 70},{"answer": " Please.  Ill have a salad with the Caesar dressing", "docId": "11-09", "aSentId": 72, "question": " All right.  Would you like to add a salad or soup to that", "qSentId": 71},{"answer": " OK.  I got it.  Your food should be out shortly.  Let me know if I can get yo", "docId": "11-09", "aSentId": 73, "question": " Please.  Ill have a salad with the Caesar dressing", "qSentId": 72},{"answer": " Thank you", "docId": "11-09", "aSentId": 77, "question": " OK.  I got it.  Your food should be out shortly.  Let me know if I can get yo", "qSentId": 76}]
